<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reno DuBois</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/</link><description>Recent content on Reno DuBois</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:15:52 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.renodubois.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>K O T O: PLATONICPLANET - Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/koto-platonicplanet-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:15:52 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/koto-platonicplanet-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
Due to a lack of a review yesterday, today we&amp;rsquo;re listening to two albums to make up for it. Today&amp;rsquo;s first album was PLATONICPLANET from K O T O (which also sometimes stylized KOTO, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure which is correct) - this album was a lot of fun.</description></item><item><title>Kero Kero Bonito: Time 'n' Place - Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/kkb-time-n-place-review/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 13:49:27 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/kkb-time-n-place-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
Next up on the docket is Kero Kero Bonito&amp;rsquo;s Time &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Place: a really nice, short album that tones down the bright and cheery electronic elements you heard in earlier KKB records and trades it in for guitars and the occasional bit of noise. I had only listened to a bit of KKB before this, and I was expecting more dancy electropop that I heard from them previously, but this album took a different direction that I really liked.</description></item><item><title>Black Country, New Road: For the first time - Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/bcnr-for-the-first-time-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/bcnr-for-the-first-time-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
I realized as I started listening to this album that even though I saw their name on every music related thing for the past year, I had zero clue what the hell Black Country, New Road even sounded like. After listening to their debut record, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I can even articulate their sound well, but oh man was it amazing.</description></item><item><title>mikgazer vol 1 Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/mikgazer-vol-1-review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/mikgazer-vol-1-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
First album of the month is a compilation album, mikgazer vol. 1. This is a collection of shoegaze instrumentals with vocals by none other than everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite vocaloid, Hatsune Miku. Part of the reason I picked this album was because of the odd pairing of those two things, but it honestly worked super well.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.renodubois.com/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 08:50:21 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/about/</guid><description>hi there! i&amp;rsquo;m reno.</description></item><item><title>Album a Day Jan 2022</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/album-a-day-jan-2022-intro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:01:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/album-a-day-jan-2022-intro/</guid><description>Howdy folks! No time to start posting things on the blog like the new year.
A friend recently suggested something I love the idea of - listening to an album you haven&amp;rsquo;t listened to before, every day for a month. I&amp;rsquo;m starting a few days late into January, but still excited to get started with this.
We&amp;rsquo;ll see how the frequency of these posts keeps up, but I&amp;rsquo;m planning on posting my thoughts on the albums I listen to here, so prepare for amateur music journalism.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.renodubois.com/links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/links/</guid><description>My email: me@renodubois.com
GitHub Sourcehut Twitter Twitch Mastodon</description></item><item><title>Coffee</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/notes/coffee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/notes/coffee/</guid><description>This is an attempt to document some of the methods I use to brew myself coffee.
It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that (like many things) coffee is subject to a lot of personal preference. Things I like doing may not be the best for you, so feel free to adjust as needed.
I mostly drink filtered coffee, using a v60, with a preference towards lighter, more acidic roasts. Almost all of the coffee I make at home I take black, but I&amp;rsquo;ll sometimes get oat milk with iced coffee at coffee shops.</description></item></channel></rss>