<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reno DuBois</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/</link><description>Recent content on Reno DuBois</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.renodubois.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Board of Comissioners Meeting</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/bistate/2023_02_17_commissioners/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/bistate/2023_02_17_commissioners/</guid><description>Date: 02/17/2023 Time: 8:33AM Meeting Materials: https://www.bistatedev.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/02-17-2023-Board-of-Commissioners-Open-Meeting-Materials.pdf Video Link: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9fhv8pY0kD8 Howdy folks, we&amp;rsquo;re back with some more Bi-State meeting notes. Apologies for these being a little bit late. The agenda for today seems to be a bunch of items I&amp;rsquo;ve covered in previous notes, so I&amp;rsquo;ll link to those for more detailed explanations on what is going on in those items.
Public comments 6 Comments: Metro Dashboard for Metrics, Safety, American Infrastructure Plan funding, &amp;amp; equitable transit operations in North County.</description></item><item><title>Audit, Finance &amp; Administration Committee Meeting</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/bistate/2023_01_27_audit_finance_admin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/bistate/2023_01_27_audit_finance_admin/</guid><description>Date: Jan 27, 2023 Meeting Materials: link Video Link: Facebook (starts at about 50:30) Hey y&amp;rsquo;all, quick note from the editor on this one. Financial reports are&amp;hellip;confusing to me as a non-financial person, so these notes aren&amp;rsquo;t the greatest ones I&amp;rsquo;ve put out. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to understand more as I get through more meetings, but just a heads up that the first few financial meetings will be a bit harder for me to make useful notes for.</description></item><item><title>Operations Committee Meeting</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/bistate/2023_01_27_operations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/bistate/2023_01_27_operations/</guid><description>Date: Jan 27, 2023 Meeting Materials: link Video Link: Facebook (starts at 00:00) Public Comment 7 in total. VIA, Rickshaws, and 5 comments from the same person regarding a few things, all of these comments are available in the minutes I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize they don&amp;rsquo;t read the comments in their entirety anymore - really wish they would! Minutes Approval done, no changes Contract Modification - On Call GEC Services Being presented by Tom Curran This is a contract for on call engineering services, it sounds like.</description></item><item><title>Safety &amp; Security Committee Meeting</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/bistate/2023_01_12_safety_security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/bistate/2023_01_12_safety_security/</guid><description>Date: Jan 12, 2023 Time: 8:45AM - 9:52AM Meeting Materials: link Video Link: not yet uploaded, will probably be available on Bi-State YouTube Roll Call
Public Comment/Speaker Cards: none submitted to safety &amp;amp; security
Minutes from previous meeting: approved
Secure Platform Plan (SPP) Update - Kevin Scott
Fencing, gating &amp;amp; CCTV Introducing some of the staff associated with the project: Chris Poehler: oversees the work of the engineering staff Time Nittler: BiState&amp;rsquo;s lead SPP engineer on the project Kelly Haidinyak: project manager on BiState Scott Streckfuest (sp?</description></item><item><title>Board of Commissioners Special Meeting</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/bistate/2023_01_12_commissioners/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/bistate/2023_01_12_commissioners/</guid><description>This meeting immediately entered into executive session, and then ajourned after that. This page is just here for record of that.</description></item><item><title>Album a Week 2023</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/album-a-week-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 12:42:52 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/album-a-week-2023/</guid><description>Wew, that whole &amp;lsquo;album a day&amp;rsquo; thing didn&amp;rsquo;t pan out so well. Instead, we&amp;rsquo;re trying an album a week this year.
The rules are simple: listening to a new album I haven&amp;rsquo;t listened to before, posting some thoughts here. I&amp;rsquo;m going to keep things in one post this time, so check back here to see what new albums I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking at.
Week 1: five seconds flat by Lizzy McAlpine # I had seen a few mentions of Lizzy McAlpine but hadn&amp;rsquo;t payed much attention until I saw her Tiny Desk.</description></item><item><title>Alvvays: Antisocialites - Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/alvvays-antisocialites-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 21:37:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/alvvays-antisocialites-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
Review number 2 today: the second album from Canadian band Alvvays, Antisocialites.
This was a suuuuuper cool album that combined a really cool voice, indie pop and the guitar tone of lighthearded shoegaze. As you might have guessed by the shoegaze record previously reviewed on this blog, I really loved it.</description></item><item><title>alt-J: An Awesome Wave - Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/alt-j-an-awesome-wave-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 21:07:50 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/alt-j-an-awesome-wave-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
Like most folks in the mid 2010s, I heard Breezeblocks on my local alt rock radio station for the first time, and thought &amp;ldquo;what a weird but catchy song&amp;rdquo;. That theme was&amp;hellip;further explored in the rest of the album that Breezeblocks was on, An Awesome Wave.</description></item><item><title>Kevin Abstract: ARIZONA BABY - Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/kevin-abstract-arizona-baby-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 21:51:38 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/kevin-abstract-arizona-baby-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
This is case for a few of the albums on my list this year, but I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I went this long without listening to Kevin Abstract&amp;rsquo;s latest album, ARIZONA BABY. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of both Kevin&amp;rsquo;s work in BROCKHAMPTON and also all things Jack Antonoff, and with the two of them coming together on this album is something I was sure to love.</description></item><item><title>K O T O: PLATONICPLANET - Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/koto-platonicplanet-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:15:52 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/koto-platonicplanet-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
Due to a lack of a review yesterday, today we&amp;rsquo;re listening to two albums to make up for it. Today&amp;rsquo;s first album was PLATONICPLANET from K O T O (which also sometimes stylized KOTO, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure which is correct) - this album was a lot of fun.</description></item><item><title>Kero Kero Bonito: Time 'n' Place - Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/kkb-time-n-place-review/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 13:49:27 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/kkb-time-n-place-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
Next up on the docket is Kero Kero Bonito&amp;rsquo;s Time &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Place: a really nice, short album that tones down the bright and cheery electronic elements you heard in earlier KKB records and trades it in for guitars and the occasional bit of noise. I had only listened to a bit of KKB before this, and I was expecting more dancy electropop that I heard from them previously, but this album took a different direction that I really liked.</description></item><item><title>Black Country, New Road: For the first time - Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/bcnr-for-the-first-time-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/bcnr-for-the-first-time-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
I realized as I started listening to this album that even though I saw their name on every music related thing for the past year, I had zero clue what the hell Black Country, New Road even sounded like. After listening to their debut record, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I can even articulate their sound well, but oh man was it amazing.</description></item><item><title>mikgazer vol 1 Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/mikgazer-vol-1-review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/mikgazer-vol-1-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
First album of the month is a compilation album, mikgazer vol. 1. This is a collection of shoegaze instrumentals with vocals by none other than everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite vocaloid, Hatsune Miku. Part of the reason I picked this album was because of the odd pairing of those two things, but it honestly worked super well.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.renodubois.com/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 08:50:21 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/about/</guid><description>hi there! i&amp;rsquo;m reno.</description></item><item><title>Album a Day Jan 2022</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/album-a-day-jan-2022-intro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:01:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/album-a-day-jan-2022-intro/</guid><description>Howdy folks! No time to start posting things on the blog like the new year.
A friend recently suggested something I love the idea of - listening to an album you haven&amp;rsquo;t listened to before, every day for a month. I&amp;rsquo;m starting a few days late into January, but still excited to get started with this.
We&amp;rsquo;ll see how the frequency of these posts keeps up, but I&amp;rsquo;m planning on posting my thoughts on the albums I listen to here, so prepare for amateur music journalism.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.renodubois.com/links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/links/</guid><description>My email: me@renodubois.com
GitHub Sourcehut Twitch Mastodon</description></item><item><title>Coffee</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/notes/coffee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/notes/coffee/</guid><description>This is an attempt to document some of the methods I use to brew myself coffee.
It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that (like many things) coffee is subject to a lot of personal preference. Things I like doing may not be the best for you, so feel free to adjust as needed.
I mostly drink filtered coffee, using a v60, with a preference towards lighter, more acidic roasts. Almost all of the coffee I make at home I take black, but I&amp;rsquo;ll sometimes get oat milk with iced coffee at coffee shops.</description></item></channel></rss>