<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>music on Reno DuBois</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/tags/music/</link><description>Recent content in music on Reno DuBois</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.renodubois.com/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Black Country, New Road: For the first time - Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/bcnr-for-the-first-time-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/bcnr-for-the-first-time-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
I realized as I started listening to this album that even though I saw their name on every music related thing for the past year, I had zero clue what the hell Black Country, New Road even sounded like. After listening to their debut record, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I can even articulate their sound well, but oh man was it amazing.</description></item><item><title>Album a Day Jan 2021</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/album-a-day-jan-2021-intro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/album-a-day-jan-2021-intro/</guid><description>Howdy folks! No time to start posting things on the blog like the new year.
A friend recently suggested something I love the idea of - listening to an album you haven&amp;rsquo;t listened to before, every day for a month. I&amp;rsquo;m starting a few days late into January, but still excited to get started with this.
We&amp;rsquo;ll see how the frequency of these posts keeps up, but I&amp;rsquo;m planning on posting my thoughts on the albums I listen to here, so prepare for amateur music journalism.</description></item><item><title>mikgazer vol 1 Review</title><link>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/mikgazer-vol-1-review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.renodubois.com/posts/mikgazer-vol-1-review/</guid><description>This is a review for my month long Album-a-Day adventure in Jan. 2022. if you want to read the other reviews, check out the original post.
First album of the month is a compilation album, mikgazer vol. 1. This is a collection of shoegaze instrumentals with vocals by none other than everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite vocaloid, Hatsune Miku. Part of the reason I picked this album was because of the odd pairing of those two things, but it honestly worked super well.</description></item></channel></rss>